(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Mark Smith needed to get a job.
There was one problem.
Mark was a bit lazy.
He wanted to do something easy.
I know, he said, I can be a
waiter.
I don't think that's the best job for
you, said his mom.
Why not, Mark replied.
He thought the job looked very simple.
All I have to do is clean tables,
said Mark, plus I would get big tips.
Mark got hired as a waiter in a
small cafe.
He soon realized his mom was right.
Everyone who ate left a big mess on
the table.
Mark hated cleaning up.
He was very slow at it, too.
He kept dropping plates on the floor.
To top it off, he wasn't very nice
to customers.
They left him small tips.
Mark was fired after three days.